jaynestars.com 2019-03-20

# JayneStars.com | Privacy Policy

**JAYNESTARS PRIVACY POLICY**

**Effective Date:** May 25, 2018

Welcome to JayneStars.com! The JayneStars.com domain and our affiliated websites are collectively referred to as “ **JayneStars** ”.  All JayneStars websites or mobile applications, including those of our affiliates are referred to as “ **JayneStars Site(s)** ”.

This “ **Privacy Policy** ” describes how JayneStars collects and uses certain personal information obtained through our public websites.

**JayneStars is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect lawfully in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (Regulation (EU) 2016/679).**

**Your use of any JayneStars Site means you automatically agree to and accept this Privacy Policy**.  
We updated our private policy to comply with the [General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/General_Data_Protection_Regulation).

**Privacy Policy**

JayneStars Media LLC operates JayneStars.com, and its affiliated websites and mobile apps. We strive to provide the latest content for worldwide fans of Asian entertainment. In order to achieve this goal, we sometimes collect information during your visits to understand what differentiates you from our other users. We respect the privacy and security of our users.

To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have prepared this statement disclosing our privacy practices. Here, you will learn what personal identifying information of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, and who has access to your information. This “Privacy Policy” describes how we collect and use certain personal information obtained through our public websites. We will not disclose it to any person or organization outside our organization, except as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Information We Collect and How We Use It**

We collect certain information from and about our users three ways: from our Web server logs, with cookies, and directly from the user.

Web server logs: When you visit our website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage.

We have collect information for non-registered users and registered users.

Examples of non-registered user information we may track include:

  * Your Internet protocol address
  * What kind of browser or computer you use
  * The number of links you click within the site
  * The state or country from which you accessed the site
  * The date and time of your visit
  * The name of your Internet service provider
  * The Web page you linked to our site from
  * The pages you viewed on the site

In order to stop spammers, we only allow registered users to comment and interact with other registered users.

**User Registration**

Registered users provide the following private information for user identity verification:

  * First and last name
  * Valid email
  * Birthdate
  * Gender
  * Country

We may ask users to re-verify that information when the user wants to delete the account or recover the account.  
The user’s private information is only visible to the registered user and never shared with third party companies.

Registered users have the option to delete the account. After an account is deleted, it can not be recovered.

Cookies: Our websites use cookies (i.e., small bits of text that our servers place into a file on your computer’s hard drive). This is used to save your preferences and login information, and provide personalized functionality. Third party vendors use cookies to serve ads based your prior visits to our website. In order to provide you with relevant promotions, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed on your browser. This technology uses information derived from unique visits and page views on the site to identify product promotions that may be of interest to you. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings, but be aware that this will disable some of the functionality on our website.

Personal information provided by the user: On our websites, visitors can register to purchase products or services, receive personalized content, participate in discussions, and participate in surveys or contests. When you register, we will ask you for some personal information. For other types of registrations, we will ask for your name, address, email address, or telephone number. We may then contact you with information about other products and services.

Finally, you may be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, we may collect personal information from you (such as an email address, system information, and problem descriptions) in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting.

If you don’t want to receive promotional materials from us or our marketing partners, you can opt out at any time. You simply need to update your preferences with each of the service to which you are registered.

**Newsletter**

If you subscribe to our daily email newsletter, you have the option to unsubscribe.

If you have questions about opting out, send an email message to [[email protected]](https://www.jaynestars.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**More Details About Information We Collect on our Web Sites**

Information about our website users and their usage is maintained in a secure environment. This information is not shared except to enforce the terms of our terms of use agreements, as set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as required by law.  However, we cannot and do not guarantee the complete security of any information you provide to us or we collect through your use of our websites.

Some of our websites make chat rooms, forums, message boards, or news groups available to you. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas is public. You should exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these areas. Don’t disclose information in these public forums that might be considered confidential.

**Who Has Access to the Information?**

We will share your personal data in the following ways:

  * As required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, or as needed in connection with the transfer of other business assets. In compliance with U.S. law, we do not share information with any unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes unless you expressly ask us to do so.
  * With agents and contractors who use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us. For example, if you register for a contest, the company that manages the contest for us will have access to your personal data.

**Links to Other Companies’ Sites**

Our websites contain links to sites maintained by companies that are not affiliated with us. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites, and we encourage you to use caution when visiting them. In particular, we recommend you view the privacy policy posted on each site.

**Ad Networks**

We serve high quality ads from various ad networks. [See the privacy policy of ad networks here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/jaynestars.com).

**Modifications to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time at our discretion as we change or expand our websites. We suggest you check this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to understand if any changes are made to it, and how we treat your information generally. We will display the “Effective Date” of the Privacy Policy on the top of this webpage.

**Questions or Comments**

For questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, or if you need assistance accessing or updating information we have collected about you, please contact: [[email protected]](https://www.jaynestars.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#1677727b7f78567c776f787365627764653875797b).
